RODRIGO COLLINS

FRONT END DEVELOPER







I am a React front-end developer with experience in creating attractive and user-friendly web applications. Throughout my career, I have honed my skills in designing and developing user interfaces, managing data, optimizing site performance, and staying current with the latest trends and tools.

EDUCATION

2021

CoderHouse

Front end developer React js 2021

Educacion IT

Advanced React Js

2009-2012

National University of Mar del Plata

Law

Jun 2006

CAMBRIDGE UNIVERSITY

Cambridge English: First (FCE)

SKILLS

HTML | CSS | JAVASCRIPT | REACT JS |
TYPESCRIPT | REDUX

SOCIAL NETWORKS

LINKEDIN https://www.linkedin.com/in/rodrigo-collins-812566209/

GITHUB https://www.linkedin.com/in/rodrigo-collins-812566209/

WORK EXPERIENCE

Front End Developer React JS

Alprestamo (Fintech), Sep 2022 - Present development and maintenance of website and web application

Front End Developer React JS

Aoki Tech, May 2022 - Sep 2022

development of apps and systems for companies

Front End Developer React JS

Gearthlogic, Jan 2022 - May 2022

software factory

Tutor React JS

CoderHouse, Jun 2021 - Feb 2023

mentoring, correction of challenges and teaching of complementary classes

Front End Developer

Freelance, Jun 2021 - Present

development and maintenance of websites and apps